# Jun Kang

718-986-0220 | jkang34@gmail.com

Github | LinkedIn

Versatile Full Stack Software Engineer experienced in JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, React, HTML5, CSS, educated at the Flatiron School. Background in customer services and physical therapy really taught me the patience of solving problems and allowed me to think outside of the box. One of the reasons that drove me to become a Software Engineer was the joy of providing solutions to help and change the lives of people on a global scale. Being in this field allows me to grow to improve myself, reminding me that learning never stops.

#### TECHNICAL PROJECTS

#### Grooveit | Demo

Users are able to learn to dance by watching videos and uploading videos as well.

- Created Auth Token to enable the user to log in and sign up.
- Allowedusers to browse through varieties of dancing videos and add/delete off their favorites using React components.
- Users can upload videos of their dance practice to track their progress.
- Each video has a section where users can comment or rate on how good the tutorial was based on their user
- Used a simple algorithm, the ratings shown in each of the videos are the average ratings of all the users who rated the video.

# Day Maker | Demo

Web application for creating randomized activities to spend the day.

- Used the controllers from the backend of the application to create randomized events for a day.
- Users are able to edit a part of the randomized day or delete the day entirely.
- When the days are generated, the users will be able to see all the past days that they've created.
- Before the users are logged in or signed up to the application, they are able to see all the restaurants and attractions that the application has to offer.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Ruby - Rails - React - Javascript - HTML - CSS - SQL - Heroku - Netlify

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Paspa Physical Therapy

Physical Therapist Aide

NYC, NY 2016 - 2018

- Managed the inventory of varieties of physical therapy equipment.
- Learned different therapy techniques in guiding the patients of their exercises.

## Jewel Bako

Server

NYC, NY

2018 - 2020

- Recommended customers in the selection and educating customers of Japanese cuisine.
- Received compliments from customers from the suggestions that I've provided.

NYC. NY

2019 - 2020

# Oshman & Barteck Physical Therapy

Physical Therapist Aide

- Assisted in the treatment of patients by securing patients onto therapy equipment, monitoring patient progress and
- Instructed and motivated patients during exercise sessions, under direction of a physical therapist.
- Observed treatment sessions to compile data on patient progress and responses.

#### **EDUCATION**

Flatiron School Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program NY. NY

11/2020 - 03/2021

**University at Buffalo** 

Buffalo, NY BA in Psychology 09/2015